Guide to the Overbrook Press Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Production Files, 1934-1969; Series III; 15; (36 boxes)
  - Publications
    - Hand, Learned, 1953-1954
      - Liberty... An Address Delivered by Judge Learned Hand of the United States Circuit Court upon the Occasion of the Thirtieth Anniversary of the Elizabethan Club on May 10, 1941 at New Haven, Connecticut (Box 16, Folder 165)
      - Rational Inquiry and the Triumph of Wisdom: Excerpt from a Speech, 1953-1954 (Box 16, Folder 166)
    - Heilbroner, Robert L., New Horizons in Economics, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 167)
    - Herbert H. Lehman, Director General, United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration 1943-1946: Tributes and Other Relevant Documents (Box 16, Folder 168-169)
    - Horton, Lawrence Maccoll, Prayer of Dedication for Yacht "Stranger" Delivered by Dr. Lawrence Maccoll Horton, Sunday, August 7, 1966, circa 1966 (Box 16, Folder 170)
    - In Memory of Richard Watson Gilder 1915-1943, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - The Institute of International Education & Duveen-Graham Present: Fulbright Artists 1949-1956 (Box 16, Folder 172)
    - Irving Lehman: Memorial Ceremonies Held at Opening Session of the Court of Appeals, Albany, N.Y., October 23, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 173)
    - Jacobs, Walter, Variation Play: A Study in the Mechanisms and Relationships of Black Movies in the Two-Move Chess Problem, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 174-176)
    - James Harvey Rogers, 1866-1939: In Memoriam, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 177)
    - Johnson, Lyndon Baines, An Eloquent Plea for Action, an Address by President Lyndon Baines Johnson before a Joint Session of the Congress, November 27, 1963, circa 1963
    - Jordan, Philip Furneaux, A Tale to Make Your Hair Stand on End, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 178)
    - Kennan, George F.
      - The Liberal Arts in Contemporary American Society, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 179)
      - Russia and the United States, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 180)
    - Kerr, Jean, Toujours Tristesse, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 181)
    - King, Edith Morgan, Harriet Hosmer: Yankee Sculptor, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 182)
    - King, Martin Luther, Jr., Letter from a Birmingham Jail, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 183-184)
    - La Rochefoucauld, François, duc de, Les Reflexions ou Sentences et Maximes Morales, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 185)
    - The Lady's New-Year's-Gift or: Advice to a Daughter, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 186)
    - Lane, Margaret, L'amitie Amoureuse, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 187)
    - Lassalle, Ferdinand, Une page d'amour de Ferdinand Lasalle: recit - correspondence - confessions, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 188-193)
    - Laurence Duggan 1905-1948: In Memoriam, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 194-198)
    - Lehman, Herbert H.
      - Faith of a Fighting Liberal: From the Address Delivered at the State Convention of the CIO, September 10, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 199)
      - In Reply to Senator George: Remarks on the Floor of the United States Senate, May 21, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 200)
    - Lehman, Irving
      - An Address Welcoming General Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 201)
      - Benjamin Nathan Cardozo: A Memorial, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 202)
    - Lerner, Max, The Battle of Detroit, 1943
    - Leyburn, James Graham, Pierson College: The First Decade 1933-1943, 1943-1944 (Box 19, Folder 203)
    - Lippmann, Walter, The Confrontation, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 204)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe, Little Rock and the Muscovite Moon: Challenges to America's Leadership, an Address by the Honorable Clare Boothe Luce, Delivered at the Alfred E. Smith Memorial Dinner, New York City, October 17, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 205)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, An Address Delivered at Los Angeles, California, January 26, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 206)
    - McIntosh, Millicent Carey, Education for What? A Challenge to Teaching: An Address, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 207)
    - McKeever, Porter, William Howard Schubart: Eulogy..., 1953 (Box 20, Folder 208)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, Great American Frustration, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 209-211)
    - Malgaigne, Joseph Francois, Conseils pour le choix d'une bibliotheque: ecrits pour une jeune fille, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 212)
    - Malik, Charles
      - The Problem of Asia: A Statement Delivered Before the Political Committee of the General Assembly, December 11, 1950, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 213)
      - War and Peace: A Statement Made Before the Political Committee of the General Assembly, November 23, 1949, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 214)
      - Correspondence relating to publications, circa 1950 (Box 20, Folder 215)
    - Mallory, Walter H., Remarks by Walter H. Mallory at a Small Dinner on the Occasion of the Council on Foreign Relations, May 21, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 216)
    - Mann, Thomas, An Exchange of Letters, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 217)
    - Mansfield, Comins, Adventures in Composition, circa 1944 (Box 21, Folder 218-221)
    - Maude, Angus, Why Is Waffle?, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 222)
    - Meredith, George, Modern Love, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 223-224)
    - Message to the People of Russia, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 225)
    - Meyer, Agnes E., Freedom of the Mind, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 226)
    - Meyer, Ernest L., Footnote on L'Amour, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 227)
    - Mill, John Stuart, On Liberty, 1940
    - Milton, John, Areopagitica, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 228)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm, Senator McCarthy McCarthyized, or, The Bitter Bit, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 229)
    - Nathan, Robert, One More Spring, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 230-234)
    - National Jeffersonian Democrats, Declaration of Position Unanimously Adopted by the Conference of the National Jeffersonian Democrats Held in the City of Detroit, August 1936
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold, American Pride and Power, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 235)
    - Nitze, Paul H., The Effect of New Weapons Systems on our Alliances: An Address, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 236)
    - Nixon, Richard M.
      - On the Results of the Election: Statements, by Vice President Richard M. Nixon and President-elect John F. Kennedy, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 237)
      - The White House: Statement by the President on the Death of Allen Dulles, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 238)
    - Overbrook Press
      - The Overbrook Press: A Check-list 1934-1940 (Box 22, Folder 239)
      - The Overbrook Press, Riverbank, Stamford, Connecticut: The Types, Borders, Rules & Devices of the Press Arranged as a Keepsake, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 240)
    - Palmer, Winthrop Bushnell, Flight Without Fear, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 241)
    - Perry, Ralph Barton, Plea for an Age Movement, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 242)
    - Phillips, H. L., Peter Gerald Lehman: January Seventeenth 1917, March Thirty-First 1944 (Box 23, Folder 243)
    - Phillips, Wendell, Toussaint L'Ouverture, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 244)
    - The Pied Printer's Primrose Path: A Typographical Nonsense Book, 1940-1941 (Box 23, Folder 245)
    - Pierson College: In Memoriam 1941-1946, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 246)
    - Pinckney, Mary Stead, Letter-Book of Mary Stead Pinckney: November 14th, 1796 to August 29th, 1797, 1944-1946 (Box 23, Folder 247)
    - Pindar, Some Odes of Pindar: In New English Versions, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 248)
    - Plimpton, Francis T. P. (Francis Taylor Pearsons), In Praise of Polygamy: Informal Remarks at Amherst College Chapel, February 22, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 249)
    - Poe, Edgar Allan, The Fall of the House of Usher, undated (Box 23, Folder 250)
    - The Presidential Electoral Vote from 1876 to 1932, 1936 May (Box 23, Folder 251)
    - Prévost, Abbé, Histoire du Chevalier des Grieux et de Manon Lescaut, illustrated by T. M. Cleland, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 252-257)
    - Prévost, Abbé, Histoire du Chevalier des Grieux et de Manon Lescaut, illustrated by T. M. Cleland, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 258-262)
    - Prévost, Abbé, Histoire du Chevalier des Grieux et de Manon Lescaut, illustrated by T. M. Cleland, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 263)
    - Prévost, Abbé, Histoire du Chevalier des Grieux et de Manon Lescaut; silkscreen stencils for T. M. Cleland illustrations, undated
    - Public Statement by Eight Alabama Clergymen, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 264)
    - Pursley, Leo, Jack Hogan, Ensign, U. S. N. R. Fighter Plane Squadron, U. S. Navy Air Corps, September 23, 1923 - January 29, 1944: In Memoriam: Funeral Sermon of the Reverend Leo Pursley... (Box 26, Folder 265)
    - Reston, James B., Arthur Hays Sulzberger 1891-1968: Eulogy delivered by James B. Reston at the Memorial Service Held in Temple Emanu-El, December 15, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 266-267)
    - Reynolds, Quentin James, "100 Percent American!" in Broun's Nutmeg, 1939 May 27
    - Rogers, Henrietta O., Bon Voyage!, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 268)
    - Rose, Billy, Nobody Important, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 269)
    - Sam A. Lewisohn 1884-1951 (Box 26, Folder 270)
    - Schubart, William Howard, Jr., From the Letters of William Howard Schubart, Jr., Lieutenant. United States Naval Reserve, 1918-1944, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 271)
    - Seaman, William E., George, Joanna, James Oakes: In Memoriam, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 272)
    - Shakespeare, William, The Poems of Shakespeare..., 1939 (Box 27, Folder 273)
    - Shepardson, Whitney H., Early History of the Council on Foreign Relations, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 274)
    - Sterne, Laurence, A Sentimental Journey Through France and Italy, 1936-1937 (Box 27, Folder 275)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1952
      - Korea in Perspective, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 276)
      - Must We Have War?, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 277)
    - Stevenson, Robert Louis, An Inland Voyage, 1936-1940 (Box 27, Folder 278)
    - Stevenson, Robert Louis, An Inland Voyage, 1936-1940 (Box 28, Folder 279-280)
    - Stewart, George, The Blessing of the Books: A Prayer, 1942
    - Supreme Court of the State of New York, 1691-1941: Exercises Upon the Occasion of the Two Hundred and Fiftieth Anniversary of its Founding, Albany, New York, May 28, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 281)
    - Thompson, Dorothy
      - The Abbey, the Museum, the Commons ..., 1941 (Box 28, Folder 282)
      - To Thomas Mann, 1937
    - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, Addresses Commemorating the One Hundredth Anniversary of the Birth of William Morris Delivered Before the Yale Library Associates in the Sterling Memorial Library, XXIX October MCMXXXIV, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 283)
    - Top Secret Correspondence: First Revealed at a Dinner of the Yale Alumni Board, February 21, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 284)
    - Twain, Mark, Three Sketches, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 285)
    - United States, National Resources Planning Board, "Our Freedoms, Rights and Obligations", 1942
    - University of Cambridge. Address by the Orator at the Presentation of the Recipients of Honorary Degrees to the Chancellor... I Present to You Another American Citizen: Arthur Lehman Goodhart, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 286)
    - Valentine, Alan, A Modest Proposal for the Care and Use of Subversives, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 287)
    - Vandenberg, Arthur H.
      - The American Position, 1948
      - On Assistance to Greece and Turkey, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 288)
    - Van Tassel, Etta May, Beyond Geography: A Few Poems, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 289)
    - The Voice of a Free Press: An Editorial from the New York Times, January 5, 1956
    - Ward, Barbara, Herbert Lehman at 80: Young Elder Statesman, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 290)
    - Warren, Earl, The Blessings of Liberty: An Address, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 291)
    - Wassen, R. Gordon, Toward a Russian Policy, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 292)
    - We Are For Douglas, Editorial from Chicago's American, Tuesday, October 11, 1966
    - Weill-Quillardet, Lucie, Report to the Board of Directors of Les Amateurs du Livre d'Art Français, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 293)
    - Weinfield, Edward, Dedication of the Herbert H. Lehman College of the City University of New York, March 28, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 294-296)
    - Weizmann, Chaim, Before the United Nations: A Plea for a Just Solution to the Problem of Palestine, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 297)
    - Wharton, Edith, Ethan Frome, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 298-305)
    - Wharton, Edith, Ethan Frome, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 306-307)
    - White, Alain
      - A Century of Two-Movers, compiled by Alain White, Comins Mansfield, Frederick Gamage, and Vincent Eaton, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 308-312)
      - F. Gamage an Artist in Chess Problems, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 313-316)
      - A Sketchbook of American Chess Problematists, compiled by Alain White, Edgar W. Allen, and Burney M. Marshall, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 317-321)
      - Typescripts, chess diagrams, and correspondence, circa 1942 (Box 32, Folder 322-327)
    - Wilde, Oscar, The Happy Prince and Other Tales, 1935-1936 (Box 33, Folder 328)
    - William A. M. Burden III, 1931-1962: In Memoriam (Box 33, Folder 329-331)
    - Willkie, Wendell, Our Way of Living Together in America Is a Strong but Delicate Fabric, undated (Box 33, Folder 332)
    - Wilson, Woodrow
      - Cabinet Government in the United States, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 333)
      - The Road Away from Revolution, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 334)
      - Woodrow Wilson at His Grandfather's Church at Carlisle: Address, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 335)
      - Woodrow Wilson: Addresses Upon the Occasion of His Ninety-Second Birthday Anniversary, December 28, 1948, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 336)
    - Wriston, Henry M.
      - Address: On the Occasion of His Election as Honorary President of the Council on Foreign Affairs, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 337)
      - The Voices of America: Foreign Affairs, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 338)
    - Yale University, Report of the President's Advisory Committee, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 339)
    - Zilboorg, Gregory, I Won't Apologize, 1938 Oct 25 (Box 33, Folder 340)
    - Unidentified proofs, undated (Box 34, Folder 341-346)
  - Ephemera
    The material in this subseries includes bookplates, certificates, invitations, memorial, stationery, holiday cards, tickets, and other items.
    - Altschul, Arthur G. and Siri, undated (Box 35, Folder 347)
    - Altschul, Frank and Helen
      - Business forms, undated (Box 35, Folder 348)
      - Holiday cards, undated (Box 35, Folder 349)
      - Invitations, undated (Box 35, Folder 350)
      - Stationery, undated (Box 35, Folder 351)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 35, Folder 352)
    - Amateurs du Livre d'Art Français, undated (Box 35, Folder 353)
    - American Political Science Association, 1947-1952 (Box 35, Folder 354)
    - Bartók Archives Exhibition, undated (Box 35, Folder 355)
    - Bell, Jeanette L., undated (Box 35, Folder 356)
    - Bennington College Alumnae Association, undated (Box 35, Folder 357)
    - Brick Church, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 358)
    - Cleland, T. M. (Thomas Maitland), undated (Box 35, Folder 359)
    - Committee for the Marshall Plan, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 360)
    - Committee for the Promotion of Advanced Slavic Cultural Studies, 1949, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 361)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1947-1961 (Box 35, Folder 362)
    - "Declaration of Independence from Bossism in the Bronx": poster for Jonathan Bingham, undated (Box 35, Folder 363)
    - Educational Institute for Research and Learning, 1958-1961 (Box 36, Folder 364-365)
    - English-Speaking Union of the Commonwealth, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 366)
    - English-Speaking Union of the United States, 1952-1969 (Box 36, Folder 367-369)
    - First Presbyterian Church, Stamford, Connecticut, 1956
    - Ferguson Library (Stamford, Connecticut), 1945 (Box 36, Folder 370)
    - Graham, Edith Altschul and Robert C., undated (Box 36, Folder 371)
    - Grolier Club, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 372)
    - James Graham & Sons
      - "Selections from a Dealer's Choice," catalog, undated (Box 36, Folder 373)
      - Ephemera, undated (Box 36, Folder 374)
      - Tom Two Arrows, "Hunted Deer," gouache on paper, undated
    - Lang family, undated (Box 36, Folder 375)
    - Lehman family, 1964-1965, undated (Box 36, Folder 376-377)
    - Macy, Helen, undated
    - Maloney, Tom, undated (Box 37, Folder 378)
    - Michael Wofsey Memorial Library of the Family & Children's Center (Stamford, Connecticut), undated (Box 37, Folder 379)
    - New York Infirmary, 1955, undated (Box 37, Folder 380)
    - New York Philharmonic, 1956, undated (Box 37, Folder 381)
    - New York Public Library, Dance Collection, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 382)
    - Overbrook Press, [1936?] (Box 37, Folder 383)
      Existence and Location of Originals
      Also stored in Overbrook Press: sign (Series III.).
    - Public Education Association. Art Committee, undated (Box 37, Folder 384)
    - Recording for the Blind
      - Certificates and citations, undated (Box 37, Folder 385)
      - Dedication of national headquarters program, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 386)
      - Label, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 387)
      - Unit Charter forms, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 388)
      - Art Committee: invitation, response card, envelope, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 389-390)
    - Robmicka Corporation, undated (Box 37, Folder 391)
    - Rural Stamford Committee, undated (Box 37, Folder 392)
    - Smith College, 1968 Oct 23
    - Stamford Camera Club, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 393)
    - Stamford Hospital, circa 1952
    - "To Chick - At Fifty", undated (Box 37, Folder 394)
    - Tompkins, Tommy, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 395)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 396)
    - Volunteer Service Photographers, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 397)
    - Wagner family, undated (Box 38, Folder 398)
    - West Hempstead Public Library, undated
    - "What Is Character?", undated
    - Woodrow Wilson Foundation
      - Award announcements, 1947, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 399)
      - Citations, 1947, undated (Box 38, Folder 400)
      - Raymond B. Fosdick ephemera, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 401)
    - Women's University Club, undated (Box 38, Folder 402)
    - Yale University
      - Citation for Dr. Nathan Marsh Pusey, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 403)
      - Pierson College, 1937-1938 (Box 38, Folder 404)
      - Silliman College, undated
    - Cards, invitations, and announcements, undated (Box 38, Folder 405)
    - Labels, gift slips, and bookplates, undated (Box 38, Folder 406)
    - Memorial broadsides, undated (Box 38, Folder 407)
    - "Miscellaneous Printing", undated (Box 38, Folder 408)
  - Other Production Material
    - Cover boards and dummies, undated (Box 39, Folder 409-412)
    - Cover boards and dummies, undated (Box 40, Folder 413-414)
    - Designs and reproduction material, undated (Box 40, Folder 415-418)
    - Designs and reproduction material, undated (Box 41, Folder 419)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 420)
    - "Freud Specimen Pages", undated
    - Layouts and trial sheets, undated (Box 41, Folder 421-426)
    - Brass stamps for binding decoration, undated (Box 42)
    - Paper samples, undated (Box 43, Folder 427-432)
- Printed Material, 1930-1967; Series IV; 10.63; (26 boxes)
  Series IV is organized into four subseries: Clubs and Associations, Typefounders, Presses and Publishers, and Other Printed Material.
  This series contains material published by other sources and collected at the Overbrook Press. It includes invitations, announcements, keepsakes and publications from professional and private associations and clubs; type specimens from American and European foundries; pamphlets, booklets, and ephemera from other printers, publishers, and artists; and other miscellaneous printed materials.
  - Clubs and Associations
    - American Institute of Graphic Arts
      - Exhibition catalogs (Box 44, Folder 433-437)
      - History, Objectives and Services, and Constitution and Bylaws pamphlets (Box 45, Folder 438)
      - Invitations and announcements (Box 45, Folder 439-440)
      - Keepsakes (Box 45, Folder 441)
      - Other publications and ephemera (Box 45, Folder 442-444)
    - Book Club of California
      - Bonanza Banquets (Box 46, Folder 445)
      - California Clipper Cards (Box 46, Folder 446)
      - California Poetry Folios (Box 46, Folder 447)
      - Letters of the Gold Discovery (Box 46, Folder 448)
      - Quarterly newsletter (Box 46, Folder 449-450)
      - Other publications and ephemera (Box 46, Folder 451)
    - Campion Society (Box 46, Folder 452)
    - Caxton Club
      - Invitations and announcements (Box 47, Folder 453-455)
      - Other publications and ephemera (Box 47, Folder 456)
    - Cosmos Club (Box 47, Folder 457)
    - Club of Odd Volumes (Box 47, Folder 458-459)
    - Club of Odd Volumes (Box 48, Folder 460-461)
    - Elizabethan Club (Box 48, Folder 462)
    - First Editions Club (Box 48, Folder 463)
    - Grolier Club
      - Gazette of the Grolier Club (Box 48, Folder 464)
      - Invitations and announcements (Box 48, Folder 465-467)
      - Invitations and announcements (Box 49, Folder 468-470)
      - Other publications and ephemera (Box 49, Folder 471-472)
    - Limited Editions Club (Box 49, Folder 473)
    - Pierpont Morgan Library (Box 50, Folder 474)
    - Princeton Print Club (Box 50, Folder 475)
    - Rounce & Coffin Club (Box 50, Folder 476-477)
    - Rowfant Club
      - Invitations and announcements (Box 50, Folder 478-480)
      - Other publications and ephemera (Box 51, Folder 481-482)
    - The Typophiles
      - Chapbook Commentary (Box 51, Folder 483-484)
      - Typophiles monographs (Box 51, Folder 485-487)
      - Other publications and ephemera (Box 52, Folder 488)
    - Clubs, general (Box 52, Folder 489)
    - Invitations, announcements, and other ephemera (Box 52, Folder 490-492)
  - Typefounders
    - American
      - American Type Founders (Box 53, Folder 493)
      - Bauer Type Foundry, Inc. (Box 53, Folder 494)
      - Continental Type Founders Association, Inc. (Box 53, Folder 495-496)
      - Other typefounders (Box 53, Folder 497)
    - European
      - Amsterdam Continental Types & Graphics Equipment, Inc. (Box 53, Folder 498)
      - Bauersche Giesserei (Box 53, Folder 499)
      - Calson Letter Foundry/H. W. Caslon & Company, Ltd. (Box 54, Folder 500)
      - Deberney & Peignot (Box 54, Folder 501)
      - D. Stempel Ltd. (Box 54, Folder 502)
      - Elsö Magyar Betüöntöde R.-T. (Box 54, Folder 503)
      - European Type Founders (Box 54, Folder 504)
      - Fonderie Ch. Boudin (Box 54, Folder 505)
      - G. Peignot et Fils (Box 54, Folder 506)
      - Girard & Cie, Srs. (Box 54, Folder 507)
      - H. Berthold A.-G. (Box 54, Folder 508)
      - Joh. Enschedé en Zonen (Box 54, Folder 509)
      - Monotype Corporation, Ltd. (Box 55, Folder 510-511)
      - Otto Weisert, Stuttgart (Box 55, Folder 512)
      - Schelter & Giesecke (Box 55, Folder 513)
      - Schriftgeißerei Flinsch (Box 55, Folder 514)
      - Schriftguß A.-G. (Box 55, Folder 515)
      - Stephenson, Blake & Co., Ltd. (Box 55, Folder 516)
      - Tetterode Foundry (Box 55, Folder 517)
      - Wilhelm Woellmer's Schriftgiesserei (Box 55, Folder 518)
      - Other type founders (Box 55, Folder 519)
  - Presses and Publishers
    - A. Colish (Box 56, Folder 520)
    - Acorn Press (Box 56, Folder 521)
    - Adagio Press (Box 56, Folder 522)
    - Advance Printing Company (Box 56, Folder 523)
    - Albert E. Hoffman (Box 56, Folder 524)
    - Albert Schiller, posters and newspaper clippings
    - Aldus Book Company (Box 56, Folder 525)
    - Aldus Printers (Box 56, Folder 526)
    - Allen Press (Box 56, Folder 527)
    - Amstutz & Herdeg Graphis Press (Box 56, Folder 528)
    - Anthoensen Press (Box 56, Folder 529)
    - Anvil Press (Box 56, Folder 530)
    - Aronson Press (Box 56, Folder 531)
    - Bartlett Orr Press (Box 56, Folder 532)
    - Beaumont Press (Box 56, Folder 533)
    - Berry Hill Press (Box 56, Folder 534)
    - Bibliographical Press (Box 56, Folder 535)
    - Black Cat Press (Box 56, Folder 536)
    - Blue Ox Press (Box 56, Folder 537)
    - Bowne & Co. (Box 56, Folder 538)
    - Brad Stephens & Co. (Box 56, Folder 539)
    - Braun et Cie Paris (Box 56, Folder 540)
    - Bremer Presse (Box 56, Folder 541)
    - Bruce Rogers (Box 56, Folder 542)
    - Cambridge University Press (Box 57, Folder 543)